virtually the place where you
build software. And today, or
for a long time, that's
meant the place where you
text at a formal programming
language. And for people who
aren't programmers, the way to
think of a code editor
is like a really souped
up word processor for programmers.
Where the reason it's souped
up is code has a
lot of structure. And so
the quote unquote word processor,
the code editor can actually
do a lot for you
that word processors, you know,
sort of in the writing
space, haven't been able to
do for people with a
lot of adding text there.
And so, you know, that's
everything from giving you visual
differentiation of like the actual
tokens in the code so
you can like scan it
quickly to letting you navigate
around the code base, sort
of like you're navigating around
the internet with like hyperlinks,
you're going to sort of
definitions of things you're using
to error checking to catch
rudimentary bugs. And so traditionally,
that's what a code editor
has meant. And I think
that what code editor is
is going to change a
lot over the next 10
years as what it means
to build software maybe starts
to look a bit different.
I think also a code
editor should just be fun.
Yes, that is very important.
That is very important. And
it's actually sort of an
underrated aspect of how we
decide what to build. Like
a lot of the things
that we build and then
we try them out, we
do an experiment and then
we actually throw them out
because they're not fun. And
so a big part of
being fun is like being
fast. A lot of the
time, fast is funny. Yeah,
fast is, yeah, that should
be a T -shirt. Like
fundamentally, I think one of
the things that draws a
lot of people to building
stuff on computers is this
like insane iteration speed where
in other disciplines you might
be sort of gate capped
by resources or the ability,
even the ability to get
a large group together and
coding is this like amazing
thing where it's you in
the computer and that alone,
you can build really cool
stuff really quickly. So for
people who don't know, cursors,
this super cool new editor,
that's a fork of VS
Code. It would be interesting
to get your kind of
explanation of your own journey
of editors. How did you,
I think all of you
or were big fans of
VS Code with co -pilot?
How did you arrive to
VS Code and how did
that lead to your journey
with Cursor? Yeah, so I
think a lot of us,
well, all of us were
originally FEM users. Pure VM,
yeah. No, no VM, just
pure VM and it's hormonal.
And at least for myself,
it was around the time
that co -pilot came out.
So 2021 that I really
wanted to try it. So
I went into VS Code,
the only platform, the only
coder in which it was
available. And even though I
really enjoyed using them, just
the experience of co -pilot
with VS Code was more
than good enough to convince
me to switch. And so
that kind of was the
default until we started working
on Cursor. And maybe we
should explain what co -pilot
does. It's like a really
nice autocomplete. It suggests, as
you start writing a thing,
it suggests one or two
or three lines how to
complete the thing. And there's
a fun experience in that,
you know like when you
have a close friendship and
your friend completes your sentences.
Like when it's done well,
there's an intimate feeling. There's
probably a better word than
intimate, but there's a cool
feeling of like, holy shit,
it gets me. You know,
and then there's an unpleasant
feeling when it doesn't get
you. And so there's that
kind of friction, but I
would say for a lot
of people, the feeling that
it gets me over powers
that it doesn't. And I
think actually one of the
underrated aspects of get up
co -pilot is that even
one is wrong. It's like
a little bit annoying, but
it's not that bad because
you just type another character
and then maybe then it
gets you or you type
another character and then it
gets you. So even one
is wrong is not that
bad. Yeah, you can sort
of iterate and fix it.
I mean, the other underrated
part of co -pilot for
me was just the first
real AI product. So the
first language model, consumer product.
So co -pilot was kind
of like the first killer
app for LMS. And like
the beta was out in
2021. Right. Okay. So what's
the origin story of cursor?
So around 2020, the scaling
loss papers came out from
OpenAI. And that was a
moment where this looked like
clear predictable progress for the
field where even if we
didn't have any more ideas,
it looks like you could
make these models a lot
better if you had more
compute and more data.