virtually the place where you
build software. And today, or
for a long time that's
meant the place where you
text at a formal programming
language. And for people who
aren't programmers, the way to
think of a code editor
is like a really souped
up word processor for programmers.
Where the reason it's souped
up is code has a
lot of structure. And so
the quote unquote word processor,
the code editor can actually
do a lot for you
that word processors, you know,
sort of in the writing
space, these haven't been able
to do for people editing
text there. And so, you
know, that's everything from giving
you visual differentiation of like
the actual tokens in the
code so you can like
scan it quickly to letting
you navigate around the code
base, sort of like you're
navigating around the internet with
like hyperlinks, you're going to
sort of definitions of things
you're using to error checking
to catch rudimentary bugs. And
so traditionally, that's what a
code editor has meant. And
I think that what a
code editor is is going
to change a lot over
the next 10 years.