virtually the place where you
build software. And today, or
for a long time that's
meant the place where you
text at a formal programming
language. And for people who
aren't programmers, the way to
think of a code editor
is like a really souped
up word processor for programmers.
Where the reason it's souped
up is code has a
lot of structure. And so
the quote unquote word processor,
the code editor can actually
do a lot for you
that word processors, you know,
sort of in the writing
space haven't been able to
do for people editing text
there. And so, you know,
that's everything from giving you
visual differentiation of like the
actual tokens in the code
so you can like scan
it quickly. To letting you
navigate around the code base,
sort of like you're navigating
around the internet with like
hyperlinks, you're going to sort
of definitions of things you're
using to error checking. To
catch rudimentary bugs. And so
traditionally that's what a code
editor has meant. And I
think that what code editor
is is going to change
a lot over the next
10 years.